Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1926-1974, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-22; 22 linear ft.; Reels 5488-5545)
  High Museum of Art, 1950, 1955, 1961-1962, 1965-1968 (see also: Atlanta Art Association; Atlanta Art Association and High Museum of Art)
  Highway Antique Shop, 1954
  R. Hill and Son, Ltd., 1960
  Hill, Ralph Nading, 1952, 1962
  Hille, Elise B., undated
  Hille and Curran, 1954
  Hilleman, Alex L., 1956
  Hiller, Paula, 1962
  Hilles, Mrs. Frederick W., 1956
  Hillman, Mrs. Joel, II., 1960
  Hillside Hospital Clinic, 1949, 1953
  Hillstrom, Richard L., 1958, 1962, 1964-1965
  Hilltop Theatre, Incorporated, 1952
  Hilsenrath, Yakov R., 1965
  Hilson, Catherine [Katy] and/or John S., undated, 1958-1959, 1961-1966
  Himel, Irving, 1963
  Himmelsfarb, Samuel, 1955
  Hines, Felrath, 1961
  Hinkhouse, Inc., 1960, 1964
  Hirsch, B., 1961
  Hirsch, E. W., 1954
  Hirschberg, J. Cotter, 1956
  Hirschl and Adler Galleries, Inc., 1958, 1960, 1963-1965, 1968
  Hirschland, Dr. and/or Mrs. F. H., undated, 1959
  Hirschland, Paul Michael, 1945
  Hirschburg, Mrs. Roy, undated
  S. A. Hirsh Manufacturing Co., 1966
  Hirshberg, Henrietta, 1961
  Hirshhorn, Mrs. Arthur, 1960
  Hirshhorn, Joseph H., 1946, 1948, 1951-1954, 1956, 1960, 1963, 1965
  Joseph H. Hirshhorn Collection, 1959-1960, 1962-1963, 1965-1966
  Hirshhorn, Lily Harmon, 1960
  Hirshhorn, Naomi Caryl, undated, 1963, 1967-1969
  Hirtt, Edgar, 1959
  Hitchcock, Alfred, 1944
  Hitchcock, Henry-Russell, 1945
  Hobbs, Henriette, 1964-1965
  Hobby, Mrs. William T., 1958
  Hobi, Inc., 1968, 1969
  Hochberg, David R., 1959
  Hochberg, Jack, 1965
  Hochschild, Walter, undated
  Hockaday, Mrs. I. O., 1955
  Hodes, Scott, 1963
  Hodge, John, 1953
  Hodges, Charles, 1968
  Hodges, Steve, 1968
  Hodgins, Eleann Treacy (Mrs. Eric), 1949-1950, 1953, 1960
  Hofer, Philip, undated, 1948-1949
  Hoff, Margo, 1954
  Hoffberg and Oberfest, 1965
  Hofflander, Jack, undated
  Hoffman, Arthur J., 1941
  Hoffman Fuel Co., Inc., 1966-1969
  Hoffman, Mrs. H., 1953
  Hoffman, Mrs. Lewis, 1957-1958, 1961
  Hoffman, Louis, 1950, 1952
  Hoffning, Hilda, 1953
  Hofmann, Werner, 1961
  Hofstra College, undated, 1956
  Hofstra University, 1963-1964
  Hogan, Carroll Edward, 1952, 1956, 1958, 1966-1967
  Hogg, Ima, 1956-1957
  Hoiles, Bee S., 1961
  Hokin, Edward, 1952
  Holabird and Root, 1948
  Holabird and Root and Burgee, 1951
  Holbrook, Alfred H., 1946-1951, 1953
  Holbrook, Hollis, undated, 1963
  Holbrook, Leona, 1949
  Holcomb, Grant, III., 1967
  Holden, C. Edwin, 1965
  Holdridge, Barbara, 1960
  Holes-Webway Co., 1967
  Holiday, 1958, 1963
  Holland-Goldowsky Gallery, Inc., 1960
  Hollister, Paul, Jr., 1960
  Holm, Marjorie M., 1957
  Holman, Bud, 1955
  Holman, Mrs. Cranston, 1961
  Holmes, James S., 1963
  Holmes, John, 1958
  Holmes, Mary Jane, 1956
  Holt, Mary B., 1955
  Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1962, 1967, 1969
  Holt, Virginia (Mrs. Benjamin), undated, 1959
  Hol[?]off, Alfred D., 1946
  Holway, Martha, 1953
  Holy Name Parish, 1960
  Home and Hospital of the Daughters of Israel, Inc., 1951
  Home Indemnity Company, 1955
  Home Insurance Company, 1952
  Hong Kong City Hall Gallery, 1963
  Honig, Victor, 1968
  Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1947-1948, 1959-1967
  Honolulu Chamber of Commerce (see: Chamber of Commerce of Honolulu)
  Honolulu Star-Bulletin, undated
  Hooper, Mrs. Arthur U., 1955
  Hoopes, Donelson F. and/or Ginny, undated, 1964
  Hooten, Bruce, 1959
  Hoover, Clara, 1955
  Hoover, Lavergne Marcus, 1965
  Hoover Processed Letters, Inc., 1958
  Hope, Henry Radford, 1944, 1957, 1961
  Hope Historical Society, 1956
  Houston Museum of Contemporary Art, 1957 (see also: Contemporary Arts Museum of Houston)
  Hopkins Center, undated
  Hopkins, Harry L., 1934
  Hopper, [illegible], undated
  Hoppin Bros. and Co., 1954
  Hoppin, Laurette K. (Mrs. Bayard C.), undated, 1952
  Horizon, 1958
  Grace Horn Galleries, 1938
  Horne, Archibald C., 1933, 1935
  Horne, Lena, 1958
  Karen Horney Clinic, 1956-1957
  Hornung, Clarence P., 1956
  Horosko, Marian, 1963
  Horowitz, Aren, 1963-1965
  Horowitz, Mrs. Arnold, undated
  Horowitz, Melvin S., 1968
  Horrochs, Carol L., 1965
  Horter, Elizabeth Lenz (Mrs. Earl), 1956, 1962, 1968
  Horton, Miles G., Jr., 1957
  Horwitch, Mrs. Arnold H., 1962
  Hoskins, Beatrice (Mrs. Arthur), 1964
  Hostetler, David, undated, 1964, 1967
  Hotel and Club Voice, 1966
  Hotel Publications, Inc., 1948
  Hotel Statler, 1959
  Hotel Winslow, 1964
  Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1954
  Houghton-Mifflin Company, 1962, 1965-1966, 1968-1969
  Hound and Horn, Inc., 1933
  Hourwich, Mr. and/or Mrs. George Kennan, 1956, 1967
  Housatonic Valley Conference Incorporated, 1941
  House and Garden, 1941, 1947, 1952
  House Beautiful, 1952, 1958, 1963
  House, Grossman and Vorhaus, 1933-1934
  House of H. Heydenryk, Jr., 1956
  House of Photography, Inc., 1956
  Housen, Mildred (Mrs. Stanley Xavier), undated, 1946
  Housse, C., 1958
  Houston Artists Gallery, undated, 1958
  Howard, Bessie J., 1935, 1960
  Howard, Humbert, 1959
  Howard, Jude (Mrs. William L.), 1961
  Howard Savings Institution, undated, 1967
  Howard, Sidney, 1937
  Howard University, 1945
  Howard, Mrs. W. L., Jr., 1958
  Howarth, Shirley, 1965
  Howe, Bruce, 1964
  Howell, Joseph A., 1964-1965
  Howell, Soskin, Publishers, Inc., 1944
  Howell, W. H., 1952
  Howells, William, 1944
  Howes, John, 1965
  Howland, Isabella, 1963
  Houston, Norman O., 1948
  Hryby, Peter, 1964
  Hu, Gilman K. M., 1964
  Hubbard, Barbara (Mrs. Earl Wade), 1958-1959, 1961
  Hubbell, J. W., Jr., 1967
  Huberman, Benjamin, 1967
  Hudson, Mrs. Barclay M., 1945
  Hudson, Mrs. C. Blaffer, 1962
  Hudson, Edward R., Jr., 1968
  Hudson Finishing Corporation, 1963
  Hudson Fixtures, 1965
  Hudson Forwarding and Shipping Co., Inc., 1934
  J. L. Hudson Company, 1949, 1957-1959, 1962-1963, 1965, 1968
  Hudson Painting and Decorating Co., Inc., 1963
  Hudson, Richard, 1962
  Hudson Shipping Co., 1965
  Huffnagle Press, 1958
  Hughes, Langston, 1948-1949
  Thomas J. Hughes Construction Co., Inc.,1951
  Hull, University of (see: University of Hull)
  Hulse, Wilfred C., 1953, 1959-1960, 1962
  Human Relations Council of Greater New Haven, Inc., 1966
  Hume, J. H., 1966
  Hunt, D. H. W., 1942
  Hunt, Dorothy, 1942
  Hunt Methodist Church, 1963
  Hunt, Raymond H., 1940
  Hunter College, 1967
  Hunter, Sam, 1968
  Hunter, Vincent C., undated, 1965
  Huntington, Christopher, 1963
  Huntington Galleries, Inc., 1952
  Huntington, Nell, 1962
  Huntington, Patricia S. (Mrs. John W.), 1960
  Hurd, Frank E. and/or Lita, 1949-1952, 1955, 1963-1967
  Hurley, Zita (Mrs. James E.), 1953
  Hurok, S. (see: Dinner in Tribute to S. Hurok)
  Hurtt, Clyde, 1959
  Hurvitz, Nathan, 1963
  Robert S. Hurwitz Advertising, 1962
  Hurwitz, Max, 1952
  Hussar, L., 1960
  Hutchins, Mr. and/or Mrs. Curtis M., undated, 1958, 1965
  Hutchinson, Mitchell, 1967
  Hutzler, Esterlee, 1945-1947
  Hyatt, Kenneth, 1934
  Hyde, Candice (Mrs. Hugh), 1964
  Mrs. Louis F. Hyde Collection, 1944
  Hydeman, Albert, 1959
  Hyman, Rubin, 1952
  Hyman, Sigmund M., 1962-1963, 1966, 1968
  Hyperion Press, 1943-1945
  Ide, John J., 1957
  Ideas, Inc., 1954
  I. F. A. Galleries, Inc., 1960, 1966-1967
  Ikonogenics Incorporated, 1963
  Illinois Bell Telephone Co., 1966
  Illinois Institute of Technology, 1962
  Illinois State University, 1965-1966
  Illinois, University of (see: University of Illinois)
  Illinois Wesleyan University, 1941, 1947, 1948, 1950, 1952
  Imbody, Ellen M. (Mrs. John Edwin), undated, 1960, 1961
  Immigration and Naturalization, 1946
  Imprimerie Union, 1964
  Independent Credit Company, 1946
  Indiana State Teachers College, 1960
  Indiana University, 1941-1944, 1946-1947, 1949-1952, 1956-1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1964, 1967-1968
  Indianapolis Art Association (see: Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana)
  Indianapolis Contemporary Arts Society (see: Contemporary Arts Sopciety, Indianapolis)
  Industrial Home for the Blind, 1961
  Ingenue, 1964
  Ingersoll, Anna, 1942
  Ingersoll, Mr. and/or Mrs. Ralph Sturgis, undated, 1933-1934, 1940-1942, 1950-1951
  Ingle, Mrs. I. Paul, 1958
  Ingraham, David, 1941
  Ingraham, Marjorie, 1964
  Inland Steel Research Laboratories, 1967
  Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1948, 1951-1962, 1965
  Institute of Contemporary Arts, Washington, D. C., 1955, 1964
  Institute of International Education, 1956, 1961
  Institute of Modern Art, Boston, 1939-1943, 1945-1947
  Institute of Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1959-1960
  Instituto Grafico Tiberino, 1962
  Instructor, 1966
  Insurance Company of North America, 1962-1963
  Interboro Elevator Company Incorporated, 1940
  Intercollegian, 1959
  Intercultural Publications, Inc., 1956
  Interior Space Design, 1961
  Internal Revenue Service, 1936, 1956, 1959, 1961-1966 (see also: U.S. Treasury, IRS)
  International Advertising Council, Inc., 1960
  International Antiques Exhibitions and Sales, Inc., 1956
  International Art Galleries, Inc., 1960
  International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1943, 1945, 1952, 1958-1960, 1964
  International Center for Typographic Arts, 1965
  International Directory of Arts, 1960, 1962-1963, 1966
  "International Exhibition of Sacred Art," 1961
  "International Exposition, HemisFair '68," 1967 (see also: "HemisFair '68")
  International Gallery, Inc., 1964
  International Graphic Arts Society, 1961
  International Journal of Religious Education, 1962
  International Political Advisory Council, Inc., 1964
  International Publishers, Inc., 1954-1955
  International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1948, 1959
  Intourist, 1959
  Iolani Palace, 1962
  Iowa State Teachers College, 1956
  Iowa, University of (see: University of Iowa)
  Iowa Wesleyan College, 1957
  Iredale Storage and Moving Company, 1954, 1956
  Ireys, John, 1959
  Iris Cleaners and Launderers, 1968
  "Irish Exhibition of Living Art," 1963-1964
  Irving, Flora (Mrs. Michael), undated
  Irving Galleries, undated, 1964-1966
  Irvington House, 1957
  Isaacs and Bernstein, Inc., 1964
  Isaacson, Joseph D., 1941, 1963
  Isaacson, Philip M., 1967
  Iselin, O'Donnell, undated, 1934, 1939-1945, 1947-1948, 1952-1953, 1956, 1963
  Isenberg, Julie (Mrs. Norman), 1963-1964
  Isham, Lea C. (Mrs. Lincoln), undated, 1934
  Israel, Bob and Susan, undated
  Israel Consulate General, 1964
  Israel, Embassy of (see: Embassy of Israel)
  Israel Government Office of Information Service, 1963
  Israel Institute of Technology, Inc., 1958
  Israel, Mrs. Justin, undated
  Israel Ministry of Education and Culture, 1966
  Israel Museum, 1965-1968
  Israel, R. A., 1967
  Israel, Robert, 1967
  Israeli Independence Ball, 1963, 1968
  Israeli, Nathan, 1961
  Italian Information Center, 1962
  Ito, Miyoko, 1954
  Itoh Gallery, undated, 1962, 1965, 1967-1968 (see also: Gallery Itoh)
  Ives, Byron G., 1952
  Ivyside Gallery, 1961
  Izbicki, Raymond, 1967
  Jacks, Grant L., Jr., 1953
  Jackson, Mrs., 1964
  Jackson, Katherine G. (Mrs. Andrew), 1951
  Jackson, Martha K. (Mrs. David S.), 1946, 1948-1949, 1962
  Martha Jackson Gallery, 1954, 1961
  Jackson, Martin, 1955
  Jacob, Joseph A., 1963
  Jacobi, Arnot, undated, 1942
  Jacobi, Lotte, 1964
  Jacobs, Gilberta (Mrs. Martin), 1963
  Jacobs, Jack S., 1959
  Jacobs, Mr. and/or Mrs. Martin D., 1963
  Jacobs, Marvin, 1962
  Jacobs, Mrs. S. Allan, 1964
  Jacobs, William K., Jr., 1962, 1964
  Jacobson, Raymond I., 1968
  Jacobson, Mrs. Walter, 1941
  Jacobson's Fine Arts, 1963
  Arthur Jaffé Heliochrome Company, 1959
  Jaffe, Henry, 1952
  Jaffe, Irma B., 1967
  Jaffe, Mildred, 1949
  Jaffe, Mr. and/or Mrs. Sam, 1949, 1953
  Jaffe, William B., 1952-1953, 1956
  Jagendorf, M., 1938
  Jager, Mrs. Eric H., 1957-1958
  James, Chris B., undated
  James, D. L., 1937
  James, Mrs. Marquis, 1942
  James, Oliver B., 1946-1949, 1951-1954
  James, Olivia (Mrs. Bayard), 1936
  James, Rebecca Salsbury, 1961
  Jamison, Juanita M. (Mrs. James E.), 1942
  Janis, H., 1956
  Janis, Martin, 1934, 1948, 1953
  Janis, Sidney, 1941-1942, 1962
  Sidney Janis Gallery, 1954-1955, 1958
  Janney Machine Corp., 1965
  Janson, H. W. (Pete), undated, 1945-1946
  Janss, Edwin, Jr., 1963
  Janus, 1967
  Japanese Ambassador, 1966
  Jaretski, Mr. and/or Mrs. Alfred, Jr., 1957, 1964
  Jarislowsky, Otti Elizabeth, 1964
  Jarislowsky, Mr. and/or Mrs. Stephen A., undated, 1953-1954, 1955, 1957-1958
  Jarocki, Barbara, 1966
  Jay-Thorpe, Inc., 1946
  Jedel, Harrison, 1961
  Jefferson, Cyrus M., 1960
  Jefferson Gallery, 1965-1969
  Jefferson Place Gallery, 1961
  Jeffries, Frances A. (Mrs. Lawrence), 1961
  Jennings, 1942
  Jennings, Elizabeth McNeal, 1953
  Jennings, Oliver B., undated, 1940, 1943-1944, 1958
  Jensen, Amy La Follette and/or Howard, undated, 1962, 1963
  Georg Jensen Co., 1955-1957, 1962
  Jensen, Lawrence N., 1958
  Jensen Productions, 1962-1963
  Jergens, Mary E. (Mrs. Andrew), 1955, 1956
  Jessar, Gayle and/or Ralph Alfred, 1958-1960, 1962-1963
  Jessup, Inc., 1950
  Jessup, Mrs. John C., 1951
  Jette, Edith K. and/or Ellerton M., undated, 1959-1960, 1964-1965
  Jewell, Edward Alden, 1932-1934, 1937, 1941, 1947
  Jewish Art Center, 1956
  Jewish Center of Buffalo, Inc., 1955-1956
  Jewish Community Center of Bayonne (see: Bayonne Jewish Community Center)
  Jewish Community Center of Bridgeport, 1968
  Jewish Community Center of Elizabeth, 1960
  Jewish Community Center of Harrison, 1961
  Jewish Community Center of Milwaukee, 1958-1961
  Jewish Community Center of Greater Washington, 1959
  Jewish Community Center of Worcester, 1965
  Jewish Community Center of Youngstown, 1952, 1958
  Jewish Community Centers of Cleveland, 1950, 1953
  Jewish Federation and Council of Greater Kansas City, 1946
  Jewish Frontier, 1959
  Jewish Heritage Foundation, 1961, 1963-1964
  Jewish Museum, 1948, 1953, 1956, 1959, 1962-1967
  Jewish National Fund, 1947
  Jewish Social Services Agency, 1967
  Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1947-1948, 1963, 1966
  Jewish Voice, 1958
  Joel, Anne H., 1967
  John-Frederics, Inc., 1942
  Johns, Mrs. Walter T., 1959
  Johnson, Ann C., 1960
  Johnson, Alden P., 1959
  Johnson, Mrs. Bruce, 1967
  Johnson, C. K., 1943, 1956
  Johnson, Carl, 1963
  Johnson, Charles W., 1966
  Johnson, D. Robert, 1965
  Johnson, Dorothy, undated, 1966-1967
  Johnson, Elaine Louise, 1952
  Johnson, Esther (Mrs. J. S.), 1955, 1960
  Johnson, Floyd, 1951
  Johnson, Mrs. Frederick W., 1960
  Johnson Galleries, 1955
  Johnson, Henry R., 1955
  Johnson, Hugh, 1935
  Johnson, President and/or Mrs. Lyndon B.,1964-1965
  Johnson, Paul, 1934
  Johnson, Philip C., undated, 1950
  Johnson, Mr. and/or Mrs. Robert S., 1960, 1964
  Johnson, Ruth Carter (Mrs. J. Lee, III), undated. 1966-1967
  Johnson, Mr. and/or Mrs. Seward, 1955, 1960
  Johnson Wax Collection, 1967
  Johnston, Dorothy M., 1953
  Johnston, Mary E., 1942
  Johnstone, D. Gordon, 1968
  Jones, 1958,
  Jones, Alfred E., Jr., 1951-1952
  Jones and Erwin, Inc., 1941-1942, 1950
  Jones, Anne, 1963
  Jones, Barbara, 1967
  Jones, Dorothy J., 1963
  Jones, Mr. and/or Mrs. E. Powis, 1949, 1951
  Jones, Mr. and Mrs. Edward Paul, 1950
  Jones, Frances Bird (Mrs. Charles S.), 1964
  Jones, Helen M. (Mrs Everett H.), 1957, 1959-1962, 1964, 1967
  Jones, Mrs. John Leddy, 1956
  Jones, John M., 1944-1945
  John Price Jones Corp., 1948
  Jones, Joyce, 1958
  Jones, Leslie, 1955
  R. B. Jones and Sons Inc., Insurance, 1946
  Joost, Nicholas, 1959
  Jordan, E., 1958
  Jorgulesco, Mrs. Jon, 1962
  Josebler[?], Ronald, 1952
  Josende, Leo P., 1956
  Josephson, Matthew, 1960-1961
  Josey, Verda, 1952
  Joslyn Art Museum, 1955, 1959-1968
  Joslyn Memorial Art Gallery, 1941-1942, 1949
  Journal American, 1958
  Journal Press, 1957
  Joyner, J. Brooks, 1968
  Judaism, University of (see: University of Judaism)
  Judis, Bernice, 1951
  Judlin Typerwriter Service, 1968
  Juhl, Finn, 1963, 1966
  Julian, Ira and/or Ruth, undated, 1963, 1966, 1968
  Julliard School of Music, 1940-1941
  Jungmeyer, Edith and/or Jack, Jr., undated, 1955, 1961, 1967
  Junior Art Gallery, Incorporated, 1952, 1955-1957, 1960-1961, 1963
  Junior Art Museum of the Des Moines Art Center, undated
  Junior Council of the Museum of Modern Art, undated
  Junior League of the City of New York, Inc., undated
  Junior League of Mount Kisco, New York, Inc., 1956
  Jurgens, John Albert, undated, 1952
  Jurin, Benjamin M., 1953
  Kaastra Gallery, 1955
  Kacheigis, George J., 1951
  Kachurin, Leon, 1961
  Kacmarcik, Frank, 1960-1961
  Kadison, Lily (Mrs. Milton), undated
  Kaerwer, Barbara M. (Mrs. Howard E., Jr.), 1958
  Kaganovitch, Max, 1956
  Kahane, Melanie, 1958-1960
  Kahn, Albert, 1937
  Kahn and Co., Inc., 1966
  Kahn, Anita, 1964
  Kahn, Mrs. Arthur, 1964
  Kahn, Charles L., 1960
  Kahn, Edmund J., 1947-1949, 1956-1960, 1963
  Kahn, Mrs. Gilbert, 1951
  Kahn, Jacob P., 1960
  Kahn, Milton, 1959
  Kahn, Olivia, undated
  Kahn, Robert I., 1963
  Kahn, Sol J., 1962
  Kahr, Mrs. Sidney, 1961
  Kaiser, I. Howard, 1953
  Kalamazoo College, 1963
  Kalamazoo Institute of Arts, 1940-1941, 1943, 1955, 1960-1962, 1966-1967, 1969
  Kalens Fine Arts, 1958
  Kalil, Ford A., Jr., 1963
  Kamath, Eugenie, 1962
  Kamens, Irvine, 1955
  Kaminiski, Josefa, 1955
  Kamperman, George, 1938, 1941-1943
  Kampermann, Mrs. Ike, 1961
  Kander, Allen and/or Juanita N., undated, 1957-1960
  Bernice Kandel and Associates, 1961
  Kane, L. M.,1949
  Kanegis Gallery, 1958
  Kanin,Garson, 1942
  Kanof, Abram and/or Frances, undated, 1949, 1951-1952, 1955, 1959-1960, 1963-1967
  Kansas City Art Institute and School of Design, 1932, 1948-1950, 1960, 1962-1963
  Kansas City Public Library, 1964
  Kansas Institute of Art, 1933
  Kansas State University, 1962
  Kansas, University of (see: University of Kansas)
  Kantor, Paul, undated, 1956, 1966-1967
  Paul Kantor Gallery, 1955-1957, 1959-1960
  Kanzler, Mrs. Ernest, 1941
  Kaplan, Alice and/or Jacob M., undated, 1959, 1962, 1967
  Kaplan, Bernard, 1958
  Elayne Kaplan Gallery, 1966
  Kaplan, Julian M., 1957-1959
  Kaplan, Mrs. Morton, 1967
  Kaplan, Phil, 1961, 1964
  Kaplan, Richard, 1968
  Kaplansky, M. B., 1959-1965, 1967
  Kaplin, Tom, 1959
  Kapp, David, 1951
  Kardon, Janet and/or Robert, 1959, 1961, 1963
  Karfiol, Bernard and/or Margaret, undated, 1937
  Karfiol, George, undated
  Karidis, Jerome, 1955
  Karner, Walter, 1963
  Karnes, Marilyn, undated, 1960-1961
  Karolevitz, Robert F., 1969
  Karolik, Maxim, undated, 1950-1952, 1954-1955
  Karsh, Estrellita and/or Yosuf, 1966-1968
  Karter, Lawrence B., 1960-1961, 1963
  Kasmin Limited, 1964
  Kass, Fred L., 1967-1968
  Kassan, Elizabeth, 1965
  Kastelas, Milton, 1955
  Kastor, Hugo, 1950, 1952-1953
  Katonah Gallery, 1956-1957, 1961-1963, 1966
  Katz, Karl, undated, 1967
  Katz, Rosalie K., 1957, 1965
  Katz, William, 1961
  Katzman, Herbert, 1953-1954
  Katzman, Sidney, 1956
  Kauder, Warren G., 1967
  Kaufman Art Gallery, 1952
  Kaufman, Beatrice, undated, 1942
  Kaufman, Dorothy, 1966
  Kaufman, Mrs. George S., 1932, 1942-1943
  Kaufman, Max, 1956
  Kaufmann Department Stores, 1956
  Kaufmann, Edgar, Jr., 1940, 1958, 1962
  Kaufmann, Steven N., 1957, 1965
  Kavanaugh, Mrs. Dunn, 1951
  Kawakami, Dan, 1967
  Kawakami, Keija, 1969
  Kay, Jane E., undated
  Kayden, Mr. and/or Mrs. Herbert J., undated, 1951, 1954, 1956, 1966-1967
  Kaye, Earl W., 1960
  Kaye, Harold, 1955-1957, 1963
  Kaye, Mort, 1956
  Kaz, Kaye, 1968
  Kaz, Nathaniel, 1941
  Kealiinohomoku, Joanne, 1960
  Kealiinohomoku, Thomas, 1960
  Keating, Mary Aubrey, 1935, 1942, 1945
  Keating, T. W., 1959
  W. R. Keating and Co., 1959, 1962, 1964-1966
  Keck, Caroline K. and/or Sheldon, undated, 1949-1952, 1954-1959, 1961
  Keefe, Mrs. W., 1941
  Keesling, Mrs. Francis V., Jr., 1961
  Kegel und Konietzko, 1966
  Keighley, Mrs. William, 1953
  Keiser, Nancy Lee (Mrs. R. K.), 1964
  Keiter, Richard. 1942
  Keith, Paul, 1964
  Robert Keith Furniture and Carpet Company, 1941-1942
  Kellenberg, Harry, 1956
  Keller, Graeme (Mrs. Erwin), 1964
  Keller, Mrs. Joseph M., 1960
  Kelley, Chapman (see: Atelier Chapman Kelley)
  Kelley, Dorothy, 1951
  Kelley, Theron L., 1952
  Kelley, William Muir, 1952
  Kellner, Mary, undated, 1943
  Kellogg, Marion B., undated
  Kelly, Andrew, 1933, 1947
  Kelly, Anna L., 1929-1932, 1935, 1938-1939 (see also: Mrs. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.)
  Kelly, Anne, undated, 1937-1938
  Kelly, Daniel M., 1964
  Kelly, Harriet (Mrs. Stephen Eugene), 1956-1957
  Kelly, Leon, 1955
  Kelly, Lillian and/or Stephen, 1955
  Kelly, Sarah Hunter, 1966-1967
  Kelly, Tom, 1967
  Kelly, Mrs., 1957
  Kem, James M., 1940
  Kemeny, Arpad, 1953
  Kemper, William T., Jr., 1954, 1956-1958, 1960, 1963-1965
  Kempner, May (Mrs. I. H., Jr.), 1964-1965
  Kemsley Newspapers Ltd. of London, 1956
  Kende Galleries, Inc., 1946-1947
  Kennebec Valley Art Association, 1965-1966
  Kennedy, Edward, 1961
  Kennedy Galleries, Inc., 1962, 1968, 1970
  Kennedy, George C., 1957
  Kennedy, Hattie Weir and/or John H., 1955-1956
  Kennedy, J. M., 1934
  Kennedy, Jane Robson, 1956
  John F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1965
  Kennedy, John H., 1955-1956
  Kennedy, William, 1966
  Kent State University, 1967-1968
  Kentucky Guild Art Train, 1961
  Kentucky Guild of Artists and Craftsmen, 1961
  Kentucky, University of (see: University of Kentucky)
  Kerby, Robert E., 1964
  Kerner, Richard, 1956
  Kerrigan, Anthony, 1956
  Kerwin, Madeline, 1941
  Ketterlinus Lithographic Manufacturing Company, 1955
  Kety, Josephine G. (Mrs. Seymour S.), 1963
  Key Productions, Inc., 1965
  Kiam, Victor, 1961
  Kieghley, William, 1949
  Kiko Galleries, 1967
  Killiam, Walt, 1962
  Kincaid, William Wallace, 1941
  Kindlers Malerei Lexikon, 1965
  King, Mrs. Alexander, 1963
  King, Alice (Mrs. Ivan), undated, 1960
  King and Higham, Inc., 1941
  King and Weese Studios, 1956
  King, Hazel, 1946
  King Korn Stamp Company, 1964
  King, Vincent G., 1964
  King, Virginia, undated
  King, William, 1952-1953
  Kingman, Betty, 1963
  Kingsley, Carter R., 1947
  Kingstein, Jonah, 1953
  Kinnicutt, Francis P., 1937, 1958-1959
  Kinyer, James M., 1958
  Kinzel, Carol, 1952, 1956
  Kiplinger Tax Letter, 1951
  Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1960
  Leonid Kipnis Gallery, 1955
  Kipp, Roy Frank, 1946
  Kipper, Katrina, 1952
  Kirk, Katherine, 1961
  Kirk, Phyllis, 1961
  Kirkbride-Bradley Art Gallery, 1962
  Kirkwood Motel, 1955
  Kiro, Nadia (Mrs. Boris M.), 1958
  Kirsch, Dwight, 1941, 1948, 1953, 1958, 1960
  Kirsch, John, 1952
  Kirstein, Lincoln, 1943-1944
  Kislova, L., 1960
  Kissin, Eve (Mrs. Benjamin), undated
  Kitchener, David, 1965
  Kiyokawa, Taiji, undated, 1962
  Klass, Enid, undated, 1966-1969
  Klawans, Harold L., Jr., undated
  Kleeman Galleries, 1941
  Kleeman, Henry, 1941
  Kleeman-Thorman Galleries, Ltd., 1934
  Klein, Eileen Ina, 1960
  Klein, Harris J., 1968
  Klein, Jerome, 1958, 1961, 1966
  Klein, Louis, 1956
  Klein, William J., 1966
  Kline, Art, 1968
  Kling, Ken, 1946
  Kling, Roger, 1965
  Knapp-Monarch Company, 1956
  Knauber, Alma Jordan, 1948
  Kneeland, Henry T., 1956
  Kneznek, S. N., 1964
  Knickerboch, D., Sr., 1956
  Knight, Betsy, 1965
  Knipschild, Robert, 1952-1954
  M. Knoedler and Co., Inc., undated, 1932, 1939, 1941-1945, 1949, 1951-1954, 1956-1957, 1960, 1967-1968
  Hans Knoll Associates, 1947, 1956, 1959
  Alfred A. Knopf Incorporated, 1948, 1954, 1957, 1960, 1962, 1964
  Knopf, Paul M., 1966
  Knopp-Hunter Galleries, 1956
  Knowlton, Monique, 1964
  Knox, Katharine McCook, 1962, 1965
  Knox, Mabel Isabel (Mrs. Alexander), undated, 1934
  Knox, Seymour H., 1939, 1940, 1961, 1966
  Seymour H. Knox Foundation, 1963, 1967
  Kobler, Virginia, 1962
  Koch, John Paul, 1966
  Koch, Pyke, undated, 1960
  Kochen, Anna M., 1959
  Kodansha Famous Artists Schools, 1968
  Kodner, Martin, 1959
  Koenig and Bachner, 1958